# **NUNTAWAT FANGRITLONG**



# **PROFILE**

I have experience in System, Network, and Cloud. I have passionate about exploring and introducing new innovations. With a flexible mindset, I'm capable of both conceptualizing network designs and managing cloud infrastructure development and administration.

## CONTACT

- **\** 080-9746514
- ✓ nuntawat.works@gmail.com
- 356/98 Bangkok,10260

# **EDUCATION**

MAHASARAKHAM UNIVERSITY
 Faculty of Informatics,
 Bachelor ComputerScience

2016 - 2019

#### INTERNSHIP

# CETA TESTSYSTEME GMBH 4 MONTH - 2020

- Configuration Webdav uses a Linux server (Debian)
- Laravel framework and (Firebird SQL)
- Angular framework and use tools (Bootstrap, Bulma, Ngx
- Bootstrap, Angular Material)

#### **SKILLS**

- Ansible for server on-prem and AWS cloud
- Squid proxy for internet
- Terraform for AWS cloud
- Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins
- Script Linux, Nginx

#### SYSTEM CLOUD ENGINEER

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Cloud Engineer (Minor Project)

FUJITSU (THAILAND) CO., LTD.

- Cloud Skills
- · AWS Cloud:
- Networking: VPC, Subnets, Transit Gateways, VPN
- Compute & Scaling: Amazon EC2, Auto Scaling Groups
- Storage & Content Delivery: Amazon S3,
- Monitoring & Logging: CloudWatch, CloudTrail
- Databases: Amazon RDS
- Proxy Solutions: HAProxy, Squid Proxy
- Azure Cloud:
- Networking & Compute: vNet, Virtual Machines (VMs), Load Balancers
- Monitoring: Azure Monitor, Metrics
- Automation & Scripting: Azure Automation Account, Azure PowerShell Script
- Identity & Access Management: SAML App Configuration for SSO
- Identity & Access Management: SAML App Configuration for SSO
   Hybrid & Migration Solutions: Azure Arc, Azure Site Recovery (ASR), On-Premises to Cloud Migration
- On-Premises and Hybrid Solutions:
- Active Directory (AD) & Azure AD Domain Services (AAD DS) Support
- Windows Patch Management, Automation with PowerShell
- Monitoring & Visualization: Grafana
- VPN & Containerization: OpenVPN, Docker
- Observability & Logging: Prometheus, Node Exporter, Blackbox Exporter, Loki, Promtail

#### System & Network Engineer

2022 - 2023

2024 - CURRENT

#### TRI PETCH IT SOLUTIONS CO. LTD.

- Network
  - Cisco Configuration
    - Switch Cisco, DNA, ISE, WLC, AP
- Windows Server and Linux
  - o Control and config Server
    - VMware ESXi
    - VCenter
    - Monitoring server
    - Security patch for all TPG servers (400 units)
    - Monthly Report
- AD Active Directory
  - Manage user account for all users TPG 13 domain
  - Manage GPO and Policy for TPG
  - o Build script replace manual action over 20 task
- Google
  - Super Admin for Google
- Project
  - o 2 Factor Authentication (2FA) Rublon
  - VA scan
  - Automate report

#### System & Network Engineer

PRO INSIDE CO. LTD.

- Network Configuration
  - Switch: Cisco, Huawei
    - Routing, VLAN, Trunk
  - Firewall Configuration:
    - Sopgos xg, Huawei, Fortigate
- System Configuration
  - VMware ESXi, Vcenter
  - Nutanix
  - NVR
  - o Storage: Dahua, Huawei, HP
- Open-source Firewall
  - o OPNsense:
  - PfSense:Ipfire:

2021 - 2022